<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Dual Power Switchgear</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/dual-power-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dual Power Switchgear on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:36:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/dual-power-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ATS-dual-power-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ats-dual-power-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ats-dual-power-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/40.png&#34; alt=&#34;ATS-dual-power-distribution-box&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
As the name suggests, the ATS dual power distribution box has two power supply lines, which are generally used in low-voltage distribution boxes. The main power supply is generally the city power, which comes from a transformer; the backup power supply is usually supplied from a diesel generator. When working, a controller is used to realize the conversion of the main supply and the backup supply: when the main supply is powered, the controller automatically closes the main supply circuit, that is, the power is supplied by the transformer; when the main supply fails, the controller will give the generator set a The start signal allows the engine to work and supply power. At this time, the backup supply circuit will be charged, and the dual power supply will automatically separate the main supply and close the backup supply. When the main power supply is restored, the standby power supply will be separated, the main power supply will be closed, and the controller will send a signal to the generator set to stop it. In fact, this is what we usually call the &amp;ldquo;self-input and self-recovery&amp;rdquo; function of dual power supplies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comprehensive protection functions: reverse power protection, overcurrent protection (completed by circuit breaker), generator set fault opening protection, overload protection (independent of switch), voltage fault protection, emergency stop function. There are other protection functions for customers to choose to configure. The dual-power automatic transfer switch is composed of a device and an automatic controller. The automatic controller is divided into three types: automatic switching and automatic recovery, automatic switching without automatic recovery, and power grid-generator. They are connected to the device to form automatic switching of different control methods and functions. switch. It is suitable for dual power supply systems with AC 50Hz and rated working voltage up to 400V and below. The switch has double protection of electrical interlock and mechanical interlock, and at the same time has the functions of overvoltage and undervoltage in any phase of the three-phase power supply, including overcurrent protection and short circuit protection in the circuit. Widely used in high-rise buildings, hospitals, shopping malls, banks, chemical industry, military facilities and other important power supply places. ATS transfer switch cabinet is used for the conversion of two mains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ATS transfer switch cabinet monitors the power supply quality of the two mains in real time (at this time, the controller can be set to three working modes: one main, two main, and no main). Self-recovery), when the main line is powered off or the quality of power supply cannot meet the load requirements, the control system will automatically transfer the load to the backup power supply. When the main line returns to normal, the control system automatically transfers the load to the main line for power supply. When there is no active use (that is, self-injection and no self-recovery), when the first mains power is cut off or the quality of power supply cannot meet the load requirements, the control system will automatically transfer the load to the second mains power supply. Only when the second mains power failure or power supply When the quality cannot meet the load requirements, the control system will transfer the load to a commercial power supply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
