<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Inverter</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/categories/inverter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Inverter on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:29:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/categories/inverter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Three-phase vector inverter</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/vector-inverter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/vector-inverter/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Vector-inverter/5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Three-phase inverter&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
The vector frequency converter is a power control device that uses frequency conversion technology and microelectronics technology to control the AC motor by changing the frequency of the motor&amp;rsquo;s operating power supply. The frequency converter is mainly composed of rectification, filtering, inverter, braking unit, drive unit, detection unit, micro processing unit etc. The frequency converter adjusts the voltage and frequency of the output power supply by switching off the internal GBT, and provides the required power supply voltage according to the actual needs of the motor, thereby achieving the purpose of energy saving and adjustment. In addition, the frequency converter also has many protection functions, such as overcurrent, overvoltage, overload protection and so on. With the continuous improvement of industrial automation procedures, frequency converters have also been widely used.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Vector-inverter/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Three-phase inverter&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frequency conversion speed regulation has been recognized as one of the most ideal and promising speed regulation methods. The main purpose of using a general-purpose frequency converter to form a frequency conversion speed regulation transmission system is to meet the needs of improving labor productivity, improving product quality, and improving equipment. The degree of automation, improve the quality of life and improve the living environment and other requirements; the second is to save energy and reduce production costs. The specific features are listed below&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Vector-inverter/4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Three-phase inverter&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New European style design, dual display + book structure&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exquisite appearance, compact size, excellent air duct design to ensure reliable heat dissipation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The whole series of modular machines, vector heavy-duty type&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built-in standard 485 communication&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built-in standard 2-way AI input 0-10V or 4-20mA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built-in standard 2-way AO output 0-10V or 4-20mA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built-in standard 2-way programmable relay output&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built-in standard 2-way open collector output&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are 5-7 built-in multi-function terminals, which can realize up to 16 speeds and 65 multi-function applications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Built-in multiple application macros (constant pressure water supply, fire inspection, CNC machine tool, spindle engraving, etc.), which can realize constant pressure water supply for one drag five, without adding a water supply controller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shell cloud function can be customized, supporting parameter setting and start-stop control of mobile phones and computers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The main technical parameters：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-main-technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-main-technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated voltage: 3-phase 380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maximum frequency: 0.00-3200.00Hz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carrier frequency: 0.5-16KHZ, the carrier frequency can be adjusted automatically according to the load characteristics&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Input frequency resolution: digital setting: 0.01HZ, analog setting: maximum frequency * 0.025%&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Control mode: open-loop vector control (SVC), closed-loop vector control (FVC), V/F control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Command source: given by the operation panel, given by the control terminal, given by the serial communication port, can be switched in various ways&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frequency source: 10 kinds of frequency sources: digital, analog voltage, analog current, pulse, serial port, panel potentiometer, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary frequency source: 10 kinds of auxiliary frequency sources, which can flexibly realize auxiliary frequency fine-tuning and frequency synthesis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protection functions: power-on motor short circuit detection, input and output phase loss protection, overcurrent, overvoltage protection, undervoltage protection, overheating, overload protection, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
