<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Non-Standard Distribution Box</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/non-standard-distribution-box/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Non-Standard Distribution Box on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/non-standard-distribution-box/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stainless-steel-series-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/stainless-steel-series-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/stainless-steel-series-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stainless steel series distribution box is a kind of distribution box designed and assembled into various control functions according to the model and specification of the components. Since the size of the box body can be selected arbitrarily, the structure is compact to a quite perfect combination. Wall-mounted installation, it can be used as a see-through window and door, and the door panel is pasted with a sealing rubber strip to prevent rainwater from infiltrating. The cabinet is equipped with a lower outlet hole and a mounting base plate, and the lower outlet hole is installed with a sealing plate when leaving the factory.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/10.png&#34; alt=&#34;Stainless-steel-series-distribution-box&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XL-21 outdoor stainless steel power distribution cabinet is mainly used in industrial and mining enterprises. AC frequency 50Hz, voltage below 500 three-phase three-wire, three-phase four-wire power system, used for power lighting distribution. The indoor device of this product series is made of bent and welded steel plates. It has a single right-hand door with a knife switch and a handle on the upper part of the right column in front of the box. The door is equipped with measuring instrument operation and signal electrical appliances. After opening the door, all electrical appliances are exposed, which is convenient for inspection and maintenance. The incoming and outgoing lines are operated by cable connection, which is completely reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outdoor stainless steel cable distribution box, suitable for urban residential quarters, industrial areas, etc., for outdoor cable trunk network branch wiring. The box is installed with steel bars, and a circuit breaker is attached for control and protection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outdoor stainless steel three-phase meter box is a distribution box for installing a three-phase meter. There is a meter reading window on the door. It is durable and mainly used in factories and businesses that require three-phase distribution network systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outdoor stainless steel single-phase meter box is a distribution box installed with single-phase electricity. There is a meter reading window on the door. It is durable and mainly used in civil buildings and commercial distribution network systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outdoor stainless steel double-door single-phase electric meter box is a distribution box installed with a single-phase electric meter. There is a meter reading window on the door. It is durable and mainly used in civil buildings and commercial distribution network systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outdoor stainless steel three-door single-phase meter box is a distribution box for installing a single-phase meter. It is equipped with a main switch, a sub-switch, and a meter door as one of the meter boxes. There is a meter reading window on the door, which is sturdy and durable. It is mainly used in civil buildings and commercial distribution network systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The series of outdoor stainless steel distribution cabinets are suitable for power transmission and distribution systems with AC 50Hz and rated voltage below 0.4kV. This series of products integrates automatic compensation and power distribution, and integrates leakage protection, electric energy measurement, overcurrent, overvoltage and phase loss. A new type of indoor and outdoor low-voltage power distribution cabinet integrating protection and other functions, which has the advantages of small size, easy installation, anti-electricity theft, low cost, strong application, aging resistance, accurate operation, and no compensation misunderstanding, etc., is an ideal power grid Retrofit preferred products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The series of outdoor stainless steel distribution cabinets are suitable for power transmission and distribution systems with AC 50Hz and rated voltage below 0.4kV. This series of products integrates automatic compensation and power distribution, and integrates leakage protection, electric energy measurement, overcurrent, overvoltage and phase loss. A new type of indoor and outdoor low-voltage power distribution cabinet that integrates protection and other functions. It has the advantages of small size, easy installation, anti-electricity theft, low cost, strong applicability, aging resistance, accurate operation, and no compensation errors. It is an ideal power grid. Retrofit preferred products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outdoor stainless steel distribution cabinet series is suitable for AC and industrial flow. It adopts standard steel and stainless steel benches, and after adding terminals to form a complete set, it is used for terminal boxes of power equipment such as transformers, circuit breakers, and mutual inductance circuits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;European-style 10kV high-voltage cable branch box is a power distribution product developed according to the actual needs of power cable engineering, which is conducive to the node connection, installation, construction and regular maintenance of power cables.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The stainless steel outdoor transformer control box is suitable for the installation of dry power, communication and traffic management equipment. It has a beautiful appearance and is fully sealed with a waterproof lock with a handle. It is the first choice for park roads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
