<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – DFW-12 Series Cable Distribution Box</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DFW-12 Series Cable Distribution Box on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DFW-12-series-cable-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/dfw-12-series-cable-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/17.png&#34; alt=&#34;DFW-12-series-cable-distribution-box&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
DFW-12 outdoor high-voltage cable distribution box is specially used at the cable node of AC 12kV cable system to distribute electric energy. Its connection method is simple and convenient, and has the characteristics of full insulation, full sealing, corrosion resistance, maintenance-free, and exposed safety parts. It solves the problems of cable &amp;ldquo;T&amp;rdquo; connection and ring network power supply with multiple incoming and outgoing lines with advanced technology. The product form can be divided into switch branch box, European branch box and American branch box. The cable connection of the incoming and outgoing lines adopts fully insulated cable joints, which are easy to install and reliable to use. The surface of the outer box is processed by electrostatic spraying process, which is beautiful, generous and safe, and can be processed in different colors according to different environments. There are corresponding cable fixing clips and grounding terminals in the box. Reliable, small size, light weight, beautiful appearance, no oil, simple installation, flexible grounding, no live electricity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;◆Fully insulated and fully sealed structure, no need for insulation distance, reliable guarantee of personal safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆The combination is extremely flexible, meeting various wiring requirements (two inputs and four outputs, one input and six outputs, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Small size, compact structure, easy installation and operation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Dustproof, fireproof, corrosion-proof, maintenance-free, suitable for any harsh environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Two-load switch type branch box can be used for ring network power supply or dual-circuit power supply, which greatly improves the reliability of power supply with a small increase in investment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Single-load switch type branch box can be used at the end of the line, which is convenient for line maintenance and repair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆The shell is made of aluminum-zinc coated plate or stainless steel plate, and painted according to the color required by the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
