<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control –  High Voltage Switchgear</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-high-voltage-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  High Voltage Switchgear on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-high-voltage-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/7.png&#34; alt=&#34;TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
TBB□-10 high-voltage reactive power automatic compensation device is suitable for reactive power automatic tracking compensation of 35kV, 10kV (6kV) buses in 220kV, 110kV, 35kV substations, and is mainly used in 3-35kV three-phase power frequency AC power systems with large load fluctuations , the use of centralized compensation still cannot meet the system requirements, often resulting in over-compensation or under-compensation. This device can detect the reactive power required by the system in real time, and then compare it with the set value to perform automatic intelligent switching operation, so that the reactive power of the system can reach a dynamic balance, so as to improve the power factor of the system and stabilize the system Voltage, reduce loss and save electricity cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equipped with ZKG or GKN type controller, the power factor and system voltage can be controlled within the set range by automatically tracking the switching capacitor and controlling the on-load voltage regulation of the main transformer. It can automatically identify and adapt to various operation modes of dual main substations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the remote automatic selection switch, various working modes of voltage regulation and compensation can be flexibly selected&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can automatically identify and display the position information of the pressure regulating switch through BCD code or one-to-one correspondence. It has control and protection functions such as synchronous adjustment of the voltage regulation gears of the two main transformers, anti-skid gears, and light gas alarm lockout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Real-time display of main transformer low-voltage side voltage, current, power factor, reactive power, capacitor switching status and alarm protection information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has the function of harmonic measurement and display, which can measure and display the high-order harmonic content of the low-voltage measurement current in real time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has alarm protection functions such as high voltage, low voltage, PT disconnection, structural failure, and main transformer overcurrent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipped with RS-485 or RS-232 high-speed data communication interface, it can realize the &amp;ldquo;four remote&amp;rdquo; function by cooperating with the integrated automation system of the main substation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high-voltage vacuum switch dedicated to modular capacitors is used, and five sets are installed in one side of the ordinary switch cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can be flexibly grouped according to the total compensation capacity, and can be divided into 6 groups with different capacities at most, and the maximum capacity of each group is 2000Kvar/5000Kvar, and it can be switched automatically according to the combination of reactive power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipped with ZSBH capacitor bank microcomputer protection device can realize two-stage overcurrent and zero-sequence voltage protection functions. When a failure occurs in a certain group, Ke will automatically cut off and block, without affecting the normal switching of other capacitor groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reactors with different ratios are configured to limit the closing inrush current and suppress high-order harmonics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordering Information:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;ordering-information&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#ordering-information&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Main circuit scheme number, purpose, single-line system diagram, arrangement diagram and distribution room layout diagram, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit wiring schematic diagram and terminal arrangement diagram.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The type, specification and quantity of the electrical components in the switchgear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear control room or the incoming cabinet needs to be connected by a bus bridge, and the rated carrying capacity of the bus bridge, the span of the bus bridge, and the height from the ground should be provided with specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When accessories and spare parts are needed, the type and quantity should be proposed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear is used in special environmental conditions, which should be specified when ordering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XGN66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:06:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xgn66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/27.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;XGN66-12-type-fixed-closed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XGN66-12(Z) box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear (referred to as &amp;ldquo;switchgear&amp;rdquo;), this product is suitable for power single busbars with a rated voltage of 3.6-12kv, three-phase AC 50hz, and a rated current of 630A-3150A. Double busbar and single busbar with bypass system are used for receiving and distributing electric energy. It can meet the requirements of various types of power plants, substations (stations) and industrial and mining enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XGN66-12(Z) switchgear is a metal-enclosed box-type structure. The frame of the cabinet is welded by angle steel. The cabinet is divided into a circuit breaker room, a busbar room, a cable room, a relay room, etc., and the rooms are separated by steel plates. open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The circuit breaker room is in the front lower part of the cabinet, the rotation of the circuit breaker is connected with the operating mechanism by the pull rod, the upper terminal of the circuit breaker is connected with the upper isolating switch, the lower terminal of the circuit breaker is connected with the current transformer, and the current transformer is connected with the lower isolating switch The circuit breaker is also equipped with a pressure release channel. If an internal arc occurs, the gas can release the pressure through the exhaust channel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The busbar room is at the rear upper part of the cabinet body. In order to reduce the height of the cabinet body, the busbars are in the shape of a row and supported by qualified insulators with a bending strength of 12kn. The busbars are connected to the busbars of the upper disconnector. isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cable room is behind the lower part of the cabinet. The supporting insulator in the cable room can be equipped with a voltage monitoring device, and the cables are fixed on the bracket. When the main connection line is the connection scheme, this room is the connection room. The relay room is in front of the upper part of the cabinet. Various relays can be installed on the indoor installation board. There are terminal block brackets in the room. Secondary components such as indicating instruments and signal components can be installed on the door. Secondary small busbars can also be arranged on the top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The operating mechanism of the circuit breaker is at the lower left position, and above it is the operation and interlocking mechanism of the isolating switch. The switch cabinet is double-sided maintenance, the secondary components of the relay room are inspected at the front, the operating mechanism, mechanical interlock and transmission part are maintained, and the circuit breaker is inspected. The main busbar and cable terminals are maintained at the back, and lighting lamps are installed in the circuit breaker room. Below the front door, there is a grounding copper bus bar parallel to the cabinet width direction, with a cross-section of 4*40mm².&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mechanical interlock: In order to prevent opening and closing of the isolating switch with load, prevent mis-opening and closing of the circuit breaker, prevent mistakenly entering the charged interval, prevent the grounding switch from being charged, and prevent the closing of the switch with a grounding knife, the switch cabinet adopts a corresponding mechanical interlock. The action principle of the interlock is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Power failure operation (operation-inspection)&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;power-failure-operation-operation-inspection&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#power-failure-operation-operation-inspection&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The switchgear is in the working position, that is, the upper and lower isolating switches, the circuit breaker is in the closed state, the front and rear doors are locked, and it is in the electric operation. At this time, the small handle is in the working position. First open the circuit breaker, and then pull the small handle to the &amp;ldquo;break lock&amp;rdquo; position. At this time, the circuit breaker cannot be closed. Insert the operating handle into the operation hole of the lower isolation and pull it down from top to bottom. Take off the handle, insert it into the operating hole of the upper isolation, pull it down from the top, and pull it to the opening position of the upper isolation, then take down the operating handle, insert it into the operating hole of the grounding switch, and push it from bottom to top, so that the grounding switch is in the closing position. position, at this time, the small handle can be placed in the &amp;ldquo;inspection&amp;rdquo; position. The front door can be opened first, and the key behind the door can be taken out to open the back door. After the power failure operation is completed, the maintenance personnel can enter and maintain the circuit breaker room and the cable room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Transmission operation (overhaul - operation)&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;transmission-operation-overhaul---operation&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#transmission-operation-overhaul---operation&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the overhaul is completed and power needs to be transmitted, the operation procedure is as follows: close the back door, take out the key and close the front door, and turn the small handle from the &amp;ldquo;inspection&amp;rdquo; position to the &amp;ldquo;break lock&amp;rdquo; position. At this time, the front door is locked and the circuit breaker cannot be closed. Insert the operating handle into the operating hole of the grounding switch, pull it from top to bottom, make the grounding switch in the opening position, take down the operating handle, insert it into the operating hole of the upper isolation, and push it from bottom to upper, so that the upper isolation is in the closing position. In the brake position, take down the operating handle, insert it into the operating hole of the lower isolation, push it from bottom to upper, so that the lower isolation is in the closing position, take out the operating handle, and pull the small handle to the working position, then the circuit breaker can be closed .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Normal use conditions:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;normal-use-conditions&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#normal-use-conditions&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;◆The altitude does not exceed 1000m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Ambient temperature: -25℃～+40℃, the average temperature within 24 hours does not exceed +35℃.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆The horizontal inclination is not more than 3°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Seismic intensity does not exceed 8℃.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆No severe vibration, shock and explosion hazard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
