<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Hexafluoride Flow Ring Network Switchgear</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hexafluoride Flow Ring Network Switchgear on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>XGN15-24-AC-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xgn15-24-ac-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/30.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;XGN15-24-AC-high-voltage-hexafluoride-flow-ring-network-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;XGN15-24 AC high-voltage sulfur hexafluoride ring network switchgear (hereinafter referred to as ring network cabinet) is a new generation of high-voltage electrical products successfully researched by our company by introducing foreign advanced technology and in accordance with the requirements of domestic home appliances and urban network transformation. Strict form test and long-term trial operation assessment, all technical performance indicators have reached the national inspection standards. The main switch, operating mechanism and components of the unit cabinet adopt the FLN36-24 type SF6 switchgear independently produced by Daya Electric Group, and its operation mode is divided into manual and automatic. Can fully meet the changing needs of the market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;XGN15-24 unit type sulfur hexafluoride ring network cabinet is suitable for AC 50Hz, 24kV power system, widely used in industrial and civil cable ring network and power supply terminal projects. Especially suitable for the following places: power distribution in urban residential areas, small secondary substations, switching stations, industrial and mining enterprises, shopping malls, airports, subways, wind power stadiums, railways, tunnels, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Altitude 1000m; (If you have special requirements, please specify when ordering)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ambient temperature: -35+40&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The average daily relative humidity does not exceed 95%; the average monthly relative humidity does not exceed 90%;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shock resistance: 8 degrees&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No violent vibration and impact, and places with fire, chemical corrosion, and danger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
