<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Control Distribution Box</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/control-distribution-box/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Control Distribution Box on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 11:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/control-distribution-box/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JP-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/jp-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 11:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/jp-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;JP series outdoor comprehensive distribution box is designed to meet the requirements of standardization, miniaturization and outdoor type of rural low-voltage power distribution equipment. It integrates power distribution, metering, protection, overload, short circuit, phase loss, undervoltage, Current over-current protection, zero line disconnection protection on the power supply side, automatic reclosing and opening, lightning protection, and capacitor reactive power compensation are integrated, providing a guarantee for safe electricity use in rural areas.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/15.png&#34; alt=&#34;JP-series-integrated-distribution-box-compensation-control-terminal-lighting&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JP series outdoor comprehensive distribution box is small in size, beautiful in appearance, economical and practical, installed on outdoor poles or transformer poles, it is a new generation of ideal power distribution products for the transformation of urban and rural power grids. This product complies with IEC439-1 &amp;ldquo;Low-voltage Switchgear and Control Equipment&amp;rdquo;, GB7251.12-2013 &amp;ldquo;Low-Voltage Switchgear and Control Equipment Part 2: Complete Power Switching and Control Equipment&amp;rdquo;, GB/T15576-2008 Power Compensation Device&amp;quot; related standard requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The box structure is separated and horizontal, and the shell is made of 2m high-quality stainless steel plate bent by multiple folding processes (or a stainless steel double sandwich composite plate with a honeycomb structure, which has properties such as flame retardant, environmental protection, heat insulation, and anti-condensation ), using special stainless steel welding process, the overall strength of the box is high after forming, the surface is as smooth as a mirror, leaving no traces of welds; the internal installation beam (plate) is treated by hot-dip galvanizing process to ensure that it will not rust within 20 years; the front and rear of the box The door is easy to operate and repair. The door is surrounded by high-elastic anti-aging sealing strips. Each door is equipped with two types of door locks, light and dark. The open lock is equipped with an anti-blocking and anti-rust rain cover; Lead seal device; the side of the box is equipped with rain-proof and foreign-matter-proof incoming cable conduits, the bottom is punched with ventilation holes and cable outlet holes, and the top is equipped with air ducts and silk screens, which are waterproof, rust-proof, dust-proof and foreign-matter-proof The function, protection grade: IP54.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The main technical parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-main-technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-main-technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transformer capacity: 30-400KVA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated working voltage: AC400V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit working voltage: AC220/380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60Hz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated current: ≤630A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
