<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Complete Set of Switchgear</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/complete-set-of-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Complete Set of Switchgear on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/complete-set-of-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/37.png&#34; alt=&#34;XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
XL-21 type power cabinet can be widely used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, chemical industry, electric power, building materials, mechanical processing, transportation, hotels, restaurants It is used for power distribution and open power distribution of three-phase four-wire power system. It provides protection for overload, short circuit and leakage of the line, and performs normal conversion of the circuit. This product is an indoor closed device, and its enclosure protection level is IP40. The product complies with GB7251.1 and IEC60493-1 and other standards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The XL-21 type power cabinet is closed and dust-proof, and the shell is made of cold-rolled steel plate, which can be used as a switching power supply. A voltmeter is installed in front of the power cabinet to indicate the voltage of the bus bar. There is a door in front of the power cabinet. , After the door is opened, the equipment inside the cabinet is exposed, which is convenient for inspection and maintenance. The XL-21 type power distribution cabinet adopts new electrical components, which has the characteristics of compact structure, convenient maintenance, and flexible line protection. The power cabinet is equipped with air circuit breaker and fuse as short circuit protection, and is also equipped with Device and thermal relay, the front door of the cabinet can be equipped with indicating electric meter, operation button and indicator light. A busbar box can also be attached to the cabinet, which is suitable for multiple parallel installations. The busbar box is bent and closed with steel plate, and its height is 300 mm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main circuit rated voltage: AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit rated voltage: AC220V/AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60HZ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated insulation voltage: 660V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated current: &amp;lt;800A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MNS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 11:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/mns-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/39.png&#34; alt=&#34;MNS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
MNS is a modular and multi-functional low-voltage power distribution cabinet, which is used in all low-voltage systems that require high reliability in the fields of metallurgy, petroleum, chemical industry, industrial and mining enterprises, and infrastructure: power distribution box motor control system. The counter structure adopted by MNS has high flexibility. According to the needs of customers or different usage occasions, various types and specifications of components are installed in the cabinet. According to the same electrical equipment, various types of feed units can be installed in the same row of cabinets or in the same cabinet. Such as: feeder circuit and motor control circuit can be mixed together. MNS is a full range of low-voltage switchgear that can meet your all-round needs. Applicable to all low voltage systems below 6300A, MNS can provide a high level of reliability and safety. Humanized design strengthens the protection required for personal and equipment safety. MNS is a fully assembled structure. Its unique profile structure and connection method, as well as its compatibility with various elements, can meet the requirements of demanding construction schedules and power supply continuity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;① In order to facilitate the installation of equipment and on-site construction, a dedicated cable channel is provided in the power distribution cabinet, and corresponding cable fixing parts are attached.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;② Each position of the drawer unit is accurately positioned and clearly indicated. And each position can be locked with up to 3 padlocks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;③The special profile structure and connection method ensure the strength of the cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;④The drawer unit adopts contact wires to be directly plugged in with the L-shaped vertical busbar, which is simple and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⑤The unique 3-section guide rail makes the drawer in and out more flexible and convenient, and the internal components and wiring can be inspected, maintained or replaced without the drawer unit detaching from the cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/42.png&#34; alt=&#34;GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
GCK low-voltage switchgear series is called combined low-voltage withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This series of products has high breaking capacity, good dynamic and thermal stability, advanced and reasonable structure, practical electrical scheme, strong series and versatility;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Various program units can be combined arbitrarily, and one cabinet can accommodate more circuits, saving floor space, beautiful appearance, high protection level, safe and reliable, and convenient maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product complies with the ICE439 standard and the national standard GB7251 &amp;ldquo;Low-voltage switchgear and control equipment&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The frame is made of special-shaped steel, and the three-dimensional plate is used for positioning, and the bolt is connected without welding structure, so as to avoid welding deformation and production stress, and improve the installation accuracy;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mounting holes of the frame and parts change according to the modulus E=25mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The internal structural parts are galvanized, and the exterior is sprayed with electrostatic epoxy powder after pickling and phosphating;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the power center (PC) incoming cabinet, the top is the horizontal busbar area, and the lower part of the horizontal busbar area is the circuit breaker room;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inclination to the vertical plane shall not exceed 5°.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinets can be widely used in power plants, substations, factories and mines and other power users. In the power distribution system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 380 V, and rated current up to 3150 A, it can be used as power, lighting and distribution systems. Electric energy conversion, distribution and control of electrical equipment.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/43.png&#34; alt=&#34;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt; &amp;ldquo;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&amp;rdquo;
GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet is a new type of low-voltage power distribution cabinet designed by our company based on the principles of safety, economy, rationality and reliability according to the requirements of the superiors in the Ministry of Energy, the majority of power users and the design department. The incoming lines include upper, lower, left, middle, right on the top of the cabinet and rear incoming lines to meet the actual needs of various projects for different incoming lines. At the same time, there is a fixed position in the cabinet for power plants and special users to install electromechanical protection and automatic devices. The product has the characteristics of high breaking capacity, good dynamic and thermal stability, flexible electrical scheme, convenient assembly, strong series and practicability, novel structure, high protection level, etc., and can be used as a replacement product for low-voltage complete switchgear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet body of the GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet adopts the form of a general cabinet, and the frame is assembled by partial welding of 8MF cold-formed steel. quality. The components of the universal cabinet are designed according to the principle of modules, and there are 20 mold mounting holes, the universal coefficient is high, and the factory can realize pre-production. Not only shorten the production cycle, but also improve work efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The design of the GGD cabinet has fully considered the heat dissipation problem during the operation of the cabinet, so there are different numbers of heat dissipation slots at the upper and lower ends of the cabinet. When the electrical components in the cabinet heat up, the heat rises and can be discharged through the slots at the upper end. The cold air is continuously supplemented into the cabinet through the slots at the lower end, so that the sealed cabinet body forms a natural ventilation channel from bottom to top to achieve the purpose of heat dissipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the requirements of modern industrial product modeling design, the GGD cabinet adopts the method of golden ratio to design the shape of the cabinet body and the division size of each part, so that the whole cabinet is beautiful and generous, and has a new look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet door is connected to the frame with a rotating shaft type living hinge, which is convenient for loading and unloading. There is a mountain-shaped rubber-plastic strip embedded in the hem of the door. When the door is closed, the strip between the door and the frame has a certain compression stroke, which can prevent the door from directly colliding with the cabinet body and improve the protection level of the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instrument door equipped with electrical components is connected to the frame with multi-strand annealed copper wires. The installation parts in the cabinet are connected with the frame by knurled screws, and the whole cabinet constitutes a complete grounding protection circuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet topcoat is made of polyester orange-shaped baking varnish, which has strong adhesion and good texture. The whole cabinet is in matt tone, which avoids the glare effect and creates a more comfortable visual environment for the staff on duty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top cover of the cabinet can be removed when necessary, which is convenient for the assembly and adjustment of the main busbar on site. The four corners of the cabinet top are equipped with lifting rings for lifting and shipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level of the cabinet is IP30, and the user can also choose between IP20~IP40 according to the requirements of the use environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
