<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – KYN28A-24high Voltage Cabinet</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/kyn28a-24high-voltage-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KYN28A-24high Voltage Cabinet on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/kyn28a-24high-voltage-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>KYN28A-24-type-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:46:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/kyn28a-24-type-removable-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/29.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KYN28A-24-type-removable-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product is suitable for three-phase AC 50/60Hz power system, used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and detect the circuit. The switchgear has two structural forms: armored cabinet and double busbar cabinet. It can be equipped with SF6 circuit breaker, VD4-24 circuit breaker, ZN72-24 fully insulated vacuum circuit breaker, and the secondary circuit is equipped with advanced and reliable control protection unit. The interior of the product adopts APG epoxy casting and reliable solid fully insulated busbar technology for full insulation design. It has good electric field distribution measures. It is a miniaturized switchgear with advanced technology, stable performance, reasonable structure, convenient use, safety and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;★ The busbar adopts heat-shrinkable insulation material or epoxy-coated insulation means to optimize the shape of the electrodes, so that the cabinet structure is compact and the floor space is reduced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ The cabinet body is made of high-quality cold-rolled steel plates and imported aluminum-zinc coated plates, which are formed by CNC sheet metal processing and connected by high-strength bolts, nuts and rivet nuts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★Insulation boards are installed in the busbar room, handcart room and cable room in the cabinet, which greatly improves the insulation level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ It can be equipped with domestic VS1-24 vacuum circuit breaker or Schneider&amp;rsquo;s VH4 type or Alstom FP series sulfur hexafluoride circuit breaker to meet the needs of different users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ The combined valve can be opened flexibly. As the circuit breaker is pulled out, the valve will automatically close and be locked forcibly, eliminating the danger of accidental contact with high-voltage electricity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ The friendly man-machine interface makes the operation of the switch cabinet programmatic and formulaic, and the operator can understand it at a glance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;★ There are more than 160 main wiring schemes, and the structure is highly adaptable to meet the needs of different users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rated voltage: 24kV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power frequency withstand voltage: 50/65kV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lightning impulse withstand voltage: 125kV&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60Hz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Circuit breaker, branch bus rated current: 3150A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated peak withstand current: 40 kA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated short-circuit breaking current: 40 kA&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated short-time withstand current: 4s&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note: The external temperature is 55°C and the rated current is 2500A, forced ventilation is required!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Normal use conditions:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;normal-use-conditions&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#normal-use-conditions&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;◆Ambient air temperature: upper limit temperature +40℃. The lower limit temperature is -15°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Relative humidity: daily average relative humidity: ≤95%; daily average water vapor pressure not exceeding 2.2KPa; monthly average relative humidity: ≤90%; monthly average water vapor pressure not exceeding 1.8KPa;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Altitude: below 1000m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆Earthquake intensity: no more than 8℃.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆The surrounding air should be free from obvious pollution such as corrosive or combustible gas and water vapor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆No place with severe vibration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;◆When it is used under the normal conditions specified in GB3906, the user shall negotiate with the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
