<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Complete Switch Cabinet</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/complete-switch-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Complete Switch Cabinet on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/complete-switch-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 15:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/pk-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/35.png&#34; alt=&#34;PK-series-microcomputer-protection-measurement-and-control-screen&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PK series microcomputer protection measurement and control panels are used in substation (distribution) substations with voltage levels of 35KV and below. Provide intelligent and networked measurement, protection and control functions for each high-voltage equipment in the station, and at the same time communicate with the upper master station in real time to realize the comprehensive automation of the substation (distribution) station. The main functions of this series of products include: various protection and measurement control of lines; various protection and measurement control of capacitors and motors; measurement and control functions such as bus section and incoming line backup automatic switching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It adopts ultra-high-speed dual 16-bit CPU system to work, with powerful functions: all measurement, control and protection units of this product use 80C196 chip launched by Intel Corporation, its speed is twice that of 8096, and the chip itself contains all peripheral circuits. Hardware design and its simplification, reasonable distribution of protection, control, measurement, communication and other functions to two CPU chips for processing, so as to ensure that tasks can be automatically switched when one of the CPUs fails, which greatly improves the processing capacity of the system. Make the system run more reliably and safely, and leave a lot of redundancy, which is beneficial to the user&amp;rsquo;s upgrade and expansion, and effectively prevents the system from working at full capacity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All COMS industrial-grade preferred chips, with extremely low power consumption for the entire screen: All integrated circuits of this product use industrial-grade COMS chips, which greatly reduces power consumption, and at the same time, the system noise tolerance is greatly improved, and the anti-interference ability is enhanced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Highly reliable design, anti-harsh environment, in line with IEC international standards: The professional design of this product is suitable for strong magnetic interference, components and connectors are reliable in contact, impact-resistant, and push-resistant. The temperature range of the working environment is wide, and the indicators of insulation, withstand voltage, impact, and anti-interference work are in line with IEC international standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The communication network is high-speed and reliable, and all devices on the network do not affect each other: this product uses a dedicated RS-485 network communication chip, which has strong fault tolerance and high reliability, and adopts photoelectric isolation, which fully guarantees the safety of all devices on the network. The interface itself also has a self-test system, which is convenient for the rapid maintenance of the company&amp;rsquo;s online faults. When a fault is detected in the communication port, it can be automatically isolated from the communication bus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/37.png&#34; alt=&#34;XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
XL-21 type power cabinet can be widely used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, chemical industry, electric power, building materials, mechanical processing, transportation, hotels, restaurants It is used for power distribution and open power distribution of three-phase four-wire power system. It provides protection for overload, short circuit and leakage of the line, and performs normal conversion of the circuit. This product is an indoor closed device, and its enclosure protection level is IP40. The product complies with GB7251.1 and IEC60493-1 and other standards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The XL-21 type power cabinet is closed and dust-proof, and the shell is made of cold-rolled steel plate, which can be used as a switching power supply. A voltmeter is installed in front of the power cabinet to indicate the voltage of the bus bar. There is a door in front of the power cabinet. , After the door is opened, the equipment inside the cabinet is exposed, which is convenient for inspection and maintenance. The XL-21 type power distribution cabinet adopts new electrical components, which has the characteristics of compact structure, convenient maintenance, and flexible line protection. The power cabinet is equipped with air circuit breaker and fuse as short circuit protection, and is also equipped with Device and thermal relay, the front door of the cabinet can be equipped with indicating electric meter, operation button and indicator light. A busbar box can also be attached to the cabinet, which is suitable for multiple parallel installations. The busbar box is bent and closed with steel plate, and its height is 300 mm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main circuit rated voltage: AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit rated voltage: AC220V/AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60HZ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated insulation voltage: 660V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated current: &amp;lt;800A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 12:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gcs-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/38.png&#34; alt=&#34;GCS-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
GCS series combined low-voltage switchgear (hereinafter referred to as GCS complete switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The basic frame of the switchgear is a combined assembly structure, all of which are fastened and connected by screws, plus doors, partitions, brackets, busbars, drawers and electrical components to form a complete switchgear with the following characteristics:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The overall size of the frame and parts and the size of the opening are changed according to the modulus E = 20mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since all structural parts of the frame are fastened and connected by screws, welding deformation and stress are avoided, precision is improved, versatility is strong, applicability is good, and it has high mechanical strength, which fully meets the requirements of the switch cabinet. various performance requirements and changes;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the MCC scheme, the interior of the switchgear is divided into three areas (rooms), the busbar area, the electrical equipment area and the cable area, and the three areas are separated by steel plates to ensure the normal operation of the line and effectively prevent the expansion of faults. When the drawer is pulled out of the cabinet, the charged body in the cabinet is not exposed, which is safe and reliable;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the PC scheme, the manual mechanisms of AH and ME circuit breakers protrude out of the door. When operating by hand, there is no need to open the door panel, which is safe and convenient;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the fixed scheme, it not only retains the characteristics of simplicity, practicality and low price of the fixed scheme, but also has the same appearance as a chest of drawers. Its interior is also divided into busbar area, electrical equipment area and cable area. The three areas are also equally It is safe and reliable to separate with steel plate or insulation board, and it is an ideal equipment to replace the old domestic fixed products;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drawers of the MCC cabinet have four standard sizes, which are 200, 300, 400, and 600 respectively. They are light in structure, easy to assemble, and high in dimensional accuracy. The four standard sizes can be changed according to the design and user requirements. The drawer unit has Good interchangeability, and there are working position and separation position, the handle can be locked by padlock, and it is in the specified disconnection position;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear is designed for two power supply and consumption types of three-phase four-wire and three-phase five-wire power distribution system. The neutral bus N line and the protective grounding bus PE line are installed on the bottom of the cabinet, and the outlet end is used Busbar connection makes it very convenient for users to connect cables;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to ensure the reliable continuity of grounding, all common parts such as drawer rails in the cabinet are galvanized;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A natural ventilation net cover is provided on the top of the switchgear without reducing the protection level of the enclosure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, the switchgear adopts the structure imitating foreign advanced cabinets, with high mechanical strength and high degree of standardization. It conforms to the IEC439 international standard and GB7251 national standard as a whole. Its protection level conforms to IP3X in GB4208 and is equivalent to IP30 in IEC529.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinets can be widely used in power plants, substations, factories and mines and other power users. In the power distribution system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 380 V, and rated current up to 3150 A, it can be used as power, lighting and distribution systems. Electric energy conversion, distribution and control of electrical equipment.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/43.png&#34; alt=&#34;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt; &amp;ldquo;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&amp;rdquo;
GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet is a new type of low-voltage power distribution cabinet designed by our company based on the principles of safety, economy, rationality and reliability according to the requirements of the superiors in the Ministry of Energy, the majority of power users and the design department. The incoming lines include upper, lower, left, middle, right on the top of the cabinet and rear incoming lines to meet the actual needs of various projects for different incoming lines. At the same time, there is a fixed position in the cabinet for power plants and special users to install electromechanical protection and automatic devices. The product has the characteristics of high breaking capacity, good dynamic and thermal stability, flexible electrical scheme, convenient assembly, strong series and practicability, novel structure, high protection level, etc., and can be used as a replacement product for low-voltage complete switchgear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet body of the GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet adopts the form of a general cabinet, and the frame is assembled by partial welding of 8MF cold-formed steel. quality. The components of the universal cabinet are designed according to the principle of modules, and there are 20 mold mounting holes, the universal coefficient is high, and the factory can realize pre-production. Not only shorten the production cycle, but also improve work efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The design of the GGD cabinet has fully considered the heat dissipation problem during the operation of the cabinet, so there are different numbers of heat dissipation slots at the upper and lower ends of the cabinet. When the electrical components in the cabinet heat up, the heat rises and can be discharged through the slots at the upper end. The cold air is continuously supplemented into the cabinet through the slots at the lower end, so that the sealed cabinet body forms a natural ventilation channel from bottom to top to achieve the purpose of heat dissipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the requirements of modern industrial product modeling design, the GGD cabinet adopts the method of golden ratio to design the shape of the cabinet body and the division size of each part, so that the whole cabinet is beautiful and generous, and has a new look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet door is connected to the frame with a rotating shaft type living hinge, which is convenient for loading and unloading. There is a mountain-shaped rubber-plastic strip embedded in the hem of the door. When the door is closed, the strip between the door and the frame has a certain compression stroke, which can prevent the door from directly colliding with the cabinet body and improve the protection level of the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instrument door equipped with electrical components is connected to the frame with multi-strand annealed copper wires. The installation parts in the cabinet are connected with the frame by knurled screws, and the whole cabinet constitutes a complete grounding protection circuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet topcoat is made of polyester orange-shaped baking varnish, which has strong adhesion and good texture. The whole cabinet is in matt tone, which avoids the glare effect and creates a more comfortable visual environment for the staff on duty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top cover of the cabinet can be removed when necessary, which is convenient for the assembly and adjustment of the main busbar on site. The four corners of the cabinet top are equipped with lifting rings for lifting and shipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level of the cabinet is IP30, and the user can also choose between IP20~IP40 according to the requirements of the use environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
