<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Complete Switch Cabinet</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/categories/complete-switch-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Complete Switch Cabinet on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/categories/complete-switch-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GGJ-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggj-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/41.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;GGJ-low-voltage-reactive-power-compensation-device&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
GGJ reactive power compensation device is used in the main circuit and branch circuits of the enterprise power system to improve the power factor and avoid the reactive power from the power system, thereby saving electricity costs. The capacitor automatic switching and cutting set device includes a multi-functional automatic power compensation controller, which has multiple functions such as automatic switching of capacitor banks, measurement and display of various power parameters, and output alarm signals. The whole set of automatic power factor improving capacitor device includes BKMJ dry-type capacitor bank, the main structure is directly constructed as each circuit contains capacitors, capacitor-specific SLFK intelligent low-voltage composite switches and high-performance fuses, which will make its maintenance very simple , under the conditions of current resistance allowed by cables or copper bars and switching switches, the capacity of the capacitor bank can be adjusted freely. For larger capacitor sets (more than 300KVAR), it can be divided into multiple cabinets and used in parallel, and each cabinet has its own independent protection system. The complete set of capacitors for low-voltage automatic power factor adjustment can be used for three-phase co-complementation, and can also be designed as a combination of co-complementation and separate compensation according to customer needs to meet various needs of customers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advanced intelligent low-voltage electronic composite switch is used as the switching element, which completely solves the surge problem when the capacitor is switched on. There is no worry of contact burnout, no heat dissipation, and no harmonic injection. It is safe and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;① High precision: The data sampling measurement adopts true effective value, the measurement accuracy of voltage and current reaches 0.5 level, and the measurement accuracy of power factor and power energy reaches 1.0 level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;② Flexible group compensation method: The mixed compensation method of combining three-phase compensation and group compensation, fixed compensation and co-compensation can be set in groups through the control panel, and each group can set its compensation mode and control parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;③ Perfect protection functions: undervoltage protection, overvoltage protection, loss of voltage protection, overcurrent protection, phase loss protection, harmonic protection and other protection measures, with high reliability. The design is reasonable, the structure is simple, the use is convenient, the anti-interference ability is strong, and the technical indicators are in the leading position in China. The standard cabinet is suitable for various occasions and occupies a small space. Simple installation, no impact on production, unattended, maintenance-free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rated voltage: 380VAC 3~; Rated insulation voltage: 660VAC 3~;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50HZ or 60HZ;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compensation method: combination of three-phase compensation and single-phase compensation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compensation capacity: 420kvar~60kvar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compensation mode: cycle switching, coding switching, fuzzy control automatic switching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fastest response time: ≤20ms;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cabinet height: 2000mm, 2200mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Width: 600, 800, 1000, 1200mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thickness: 600, 800, 1000mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protection class: IP30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
