<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Automatic Compensation Cabinet</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/automatic-compensation-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Automatic Compensation Cabinet on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/automatic-compensation-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/tbb-10-high-voltage-reactive-power-automatic-compensation-device/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/7.png&#34; alt=&#34;TBB-10-High-Voltage-Reactive-Power-Automatic-Compensation-Device&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
TBB□-10 high-voltage reactive power automatic compensation device is suitable for reactive power automatic tracking compensation of 35kV, 10kV (6kV) buses in 220kV, 110kV, 35kV substations, and is mainly used in 3-35kV three-phase power frequency AC power systems with large load fluctuations , the use of centralized compensation still cannot meet the system requirements, often resulting in over-compensation or under-compensation. This device can detect the reactive power required by the system in real time, and then compare it with the set value to perform automatic intelligent switching operation, so that the reactive power of the system can reach a dynamic balance, so as to improve the power factor of the system and stabilize the system Voltage, reduce loss and save electricity cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equipped with ZKG or GKN type controller, the power factor and system voltage can be controlled within the set range by automatically tracking the switching capacitor and controlling the on-load voltage regulation of the main transformer. It can automatically identify and adapt to various operation modes of dual main substations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the remote automatic selection switch, various working modes of voltage regulation and compensation can be flexibly selected&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can automatically identify and display the position information of the pressure regulating switch through BCD code or one-to-one correspondence. It has control and protection functions such as synchronous adjustment of the voltage regulation gears of the two main transformers, anti-skid gears, and light gas alarm lockout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Real-time display of main transformer low-voltage side voltage, current, power factor, reactive power, capacitor switching status and alarm protection information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has the function of harmonic measurement and display, which can measure and display the high-order harmonic content of the low-voltage measurement current in real time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has alarm protection functions such as high voltage, low voltage, PT disconnection, structural failure, and main transformer overcurrent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipped with RS-485 or RS-232 high-speed data communication interface, it can realize the &amp;ldquo;four remote&amp;rdquo; function by cooperating with the integrated automation system of the main substation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high-voltage vacuum switch dedicated to modular capacitors is used, and five sets are installed in one side of the ordinary switch cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can be flexibly grouped according to the total compensation capacity, and can be divided into 6 groups with different capacities at most, and the maximum capacity of each group is 2000Kvar/5000Kvar, and it can be switched automatically according to the combination of reactive power.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Equipped with ZSBH capacitor bank microcomputer protection device can realize two-stage overcurrent and zero-sequence voltage protection functions. When a failure occurs in a certain group, Ke will automatically cut off and block, without affecting the normal switching of other capacitor groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reactors with different ratios are configured to limit the closing inrush current and suppress high-order harmonics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordering Information:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;ordering-information&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#ordering-information&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Main circuit scheme number, purpose, single-line system diagram, arrangement diagram and distribution room layout diagram, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit wiring schematic diagram and terminal arrangement diagram.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The type, specification and quantity of the electrical components in the switchgear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear control room or the incoming cabinet needs to be connected by a bus bridge, and the rated carrying capacity of the bus bridge, the span of the bus bridge, and the height from the ground should be provided with specific requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When accessories and spare parts are needed, the type and quantity should be proposed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The switchgear is used in special environmental conditions, which should be specified when ordering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
