<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Low Voltage Switch Cabinet</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/low-voltage-switch-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Low Voltage Switch Cabinet on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/low-voltage-switch-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 13:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xl-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/37.png&#34; alt=&#34;XL-21-type-floor-distribution-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
XL-21 type power cabinet can be widely used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, chemical industry, electric power, building materials, mechanical processing, transportation, hotels, restaurants It is used for power distribution and open power distribution of three-phase four-wire power system. It provides protection for overload, short circuit and leakage of the line, and performs normal conversion of the circuit. This product is an indoor closed device, and its enclosure protection level is IP40. The product complies with GB7251.1 and IEC60493-1 and other standards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The XL-21 type power cabinet is closed and dust-proof, and the shell is made of cold-rolled steel plate, which can be used as a switching power supply. A voltmeter is installed in front of the power cabinet to indicate the voltage of the bus bar. There is a door in front of the power cabinet. , After the door is opened, the equipment inside the cabinet is exposed, which is convenient for inspection and maintenance. The XL-21 type power distribution cabinet adopts new electrical components, which has the characteristics of compact structure, convenient maintenance, and flexible line protection. The power cabinet is equipped with air circuit breaker and fuse as short circuit protection, and is also equipped with Device and thermal relay, the front door of the cabinet can be equipped with indicating electric meter, operation button and indicator light. A busbar box can also be attached to the cabinet, which is suitable for multiple parallel installations. The busbar box is bent and closed with steel plate, and its height is 300 mm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main circuit rated voltage: AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auxiliary circuit rated voltage: AC220V/AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60HZ&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated insulation voltage: 660V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated current: &amp;lt;800A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
