<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Outdoor Switch</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/outdoor-switch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Outdoor Switch on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:29:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/outdoor-switch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/fzw28-12f-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/FZW28-12F/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;FZW28-12F outdoor boundary vacuum load switch&lt;/strong&gt; is used in the occasion of column installation, and has manual and electric operation functions. The switch body adopts VSP5-12 imported from Japan Toshiba Company, and this switch is a maintenance-free load switch. Vacuum arc extinguishing and SF6 gas are used as the ground and phase insulation medium. This product complies with: GB3804 &amp;ldquo;High Voltage AC Load Switch&amp;rdquo; and GBT11022 &amp;ldquo;Common Technical Requirements for High Voltage Switchgear and Control Equipment Standards&amp;rdquo;. This instruction describes the structure, function and assembly method of the vacuum load switch on the column. FZW28(A)-12F outdoor boundary vacuum load switch (VSP5-12 switch body and FDR-01 controller) has fault detection function, protection control function and communication function. It is installed on 10KV overhead line and can realize automatic cutting of single phase Ground faults and phase-to-phase short-circuit faults are automatically isolated. The installation point is suitable for the responsibility demarcation point of the user&amp;rsquo;s incoming line of 10KV distribution line, and it can also be applied for the branch line connection that meets the requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/FZW28-12F/2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/FZW28-12F/3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/FZW28-12F/4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
1.Reliable sealing performance:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With mature sealing shell technology, the shell protection level reaches IP67, and the shell is processed by one-time mold stretching molding process, which is easy to seal the box, with high air tightness and high mechanical strength;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.maintenance-free:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main circuit of the load switch, the secondary components and the operating mechanism are all sealed in SF6 gas (zero gauge pressure), not affected by the external environment, with stable and reliable performance and maintenance-free;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.Excellent line performance:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Porcelain sheathed cables or silicon rubber corner bushings are used to lead out, so that the phase distance can reach 280mm, and the external insulation performance is excellent;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.Safe to use:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An explosion-proof device is installed on the top of the box, which can effectively prevent high-temperature gas or splashes from flying out when the switch fails;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.Flexible installation methods:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It can be hoisted on the pole or installed by sitting on the pole;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.Unique features:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has unique functions such as automatic removal of single-phase ground faults, automatic isolation of short-circuit faults between phases, rapid location of fault points and monitoring of user loads, three-stage protection, reclosing, and remote communication;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;External dimensions：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;external-dimensions&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#external-dimensions&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/FZW28-12F/5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;FZW28-12F-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:29:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/vsp5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/VSP5-12/3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
VSP5-12 series outdoor vacuum boundary switch is a combination circuit breaker with isolation, rated voltage 12KV, three-phase AC 50HZ high-voltage outdoor switchgear, the built-in voltage 12KV is converted to 220V operating voltage, mainly used for switching on and off rural power grids and urban power grids And load current, overload current, short circuit current of small power system. The overall structure of the product is a three-phase common box type. The three-phase vacuum interrupter is placed in a metal box, and the SMC insulation material is used for phase insulation and ground insulation.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/VSP5-12/4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/VSP5-12/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/VSP5-12/2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;VSP5-12-outdoor-vacuum-boundary-switch&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideal equipment for urban and rural power grid reconstruction:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vacuum circuit breaker and the intelligent controller can form an automatic recloser to realize the function of the recloser, as well as remote control, remote measurement, remote signaling and remote adjustment;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible and convenient operation:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product is electric energy storage, electric separation and closing, at the same time has manual energy storage, manual separation and closing, and can be operated by remote control at close or long distances;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Superior breaking performance:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Break short-circuit current 20KA (25KA) up to 30 times;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low operating power and high reliability:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The newly designed small electric spring mechanism reduces the number of parts and the operating power (about 30W) to the lowest level;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With maintenance-free features:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main circuit of the circuit breaker, the secondary components and the operating mechanism are all sealed in SF6 gas (zero gauge pressure) and are not affected by the external environment;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reliable sealing performance:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using mature sealing structure technology, the sealing performance is reliable;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;7&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unique way of entering and exiting the line:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The silicone rubber sleeve is used to make the insulation distance between the terminals sufficient, and the external insulation performance is excellent;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use safety:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An explosion-proof device is installed on the top of the box, even if an unexpected internal failure occurs, no high-temperature gas or splash will leak out;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
