<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – Box Type Substation</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/box-type-substation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Box Type Substation on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/box-type-substation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>YB33-wind-power-box-type-substation</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/yb33-wind-power-box-type-substation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/yb33-wind-power-box-type-substation/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/19.png&#34; alt=&#34;YB33-wind-power-box-type-substation&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
It is widely used in cable distribution in 40.5KV (17.5KV, 24KV, 35KV) power systems, cable distribution boxes and transition boxes in wind farm projects. Its connection method is simple, flexible, convenient, safe and reliable. The cabinet body is made of 2 mm stainless steel plate, which is strong and durable. The live part is fully insulated and fully sealed. This product is widely used in urban industrial districts, residential districts, commercial centers, mining areas, large enterprises such as steel, automobile, petroleum, chemical industry, cement and other occasions in the distribution network, especially suitable for urban power grid reconstruction projects, which can greatly save electrical equipment and Cable investment to improve power supply reliability. FKRN-40.5/630 high-voltage load switch is attached to the cable distribution box, and the melt current specification (A) of the high-voltage current-limiting fuse: 6.3, 10, 16, 20, 25, 31.5, 40, 50, 63.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The box substation integrates high and low voltage primary equipment, transformers, and secondary equipment in a double-layer, sealed, anti-corrosion, and movable outdoor box in the factory. Box-type substation, also known as prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution device arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. Together, they are installed in a moisture-proof, rust-proof, dust-proof, rodent-proof, fire-proof, theft-proof, heat-insulated, fully enclosed, and movable steel structure box, which is especially suitable for urban network construction and transformation. A brand new substation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The box-type substation is suitable for mines, factories, enterprises, oil and gas fields, and wind power stations. It replaces the original civil engineering power distribution room and power distribution station, and becomes a new type of complete power transformation and distribution device. The overall structure of the box transformer is mainly divided into three parts: high-voltage switchgear, transformer and low-voltage power distribution device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The front part is the wiring cabinet, which includes high and low voltage terminals, high voltage load switch, plug-in fuse, high voltage tap changer operating handle, oil level gauge, oil temperature gauge, etc.; the rear part is the oil tank body, heat sink, transformer winding , iron core, high voltage load switch and plug-in fuse are all in the oil tank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The box adopts a fully sealed structure. The integrated box change has been developed by domestic manufacturers recently, and it is not widely used. It is a double-layer structure. European, American, and integrated box changes have their own advantages and disadvantages. In a large shell, the heat dissipation condition is poor, and a mechanical exhaust device is required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;American-style box-type transformers have relatively good heat dissipation conditions because the transformer cooling fins directly dissipate heat to the outside. The integrated box-type substation occupies less land, and its advantages and disadvantages are similar to those of the American-style box-type substation. In addition, American-style and integrated transformers can only be manufactured in China with a capacity of less than 630kVA, while European-style transformers can reach 1250kVA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are no less than 2 copper grounding terminals connected to the grounding grid on the grounding conductor of the YB33 wind power box-type substation, and the electrical contact area is not less than 160mm2. The grounding conductor is a copper conductor, and when the rated short-circuit duration is 1s, its current density does not exceed 200A/mm2; when the rated short-circuit duration is 2s, its current density does not exceed 140A/mm2; when the rated short-circuit duration is 3s , its current density does not exceed 125A/mm2; when the rated short-circuit duration is 4s, its current density does not exceed 110A/mm2, and its minimum cross-section is not less than 30mm2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Components connected to the grounding conductor include: box-type substation shell (metal part), switchgear frame or shell (metal part), grounding conductor and metal shielding of cables, metal frame of transformer, grounding conductor of control and protection devices, etc. A sufficient number of grounding terminals are installed on the grounding conductor, and the grounding terminals are made of copper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZBW-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-European-style</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/21.png&#34; alt=&#34;ZBW-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-European-style&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
The box-type substation is a frame structure, which is welded with section steel; the shell is made of aluminum alloy plate, coated with special paint. There are four pull-out hanging bolts on both sides of the box-type substation base, and four lifting rope support cards on both sides of the top eaves of the box-type substation. This special design for hoisting greatly facilitates the safe hoisting of the substation and prevents the sling from scratching the casing, which is highly praised by users. The box substation is divided into relatively independent high and low voltage rooms and transformer rooms by steel plates. The low voltage room and transformer room can have corridors or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adopting three cooling measures: upper and lower natural wind convection, horizontal natural wind convection and bottom special fan forced air cooling, the temperature rise has a large margin;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Light weight, small size and high rigidity;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modularization: the high and low voltage electrical room, transformer room, metering box, and capacitor box are each formed into modules, which can be selected and combined according to user needs;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beautiful appearance, low noise, in harmony with the surrounding environment and increase the beauty;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powerful functions, complete facilities, high voltage can meet the ring network power supply, low voltage room can have 8 power outlets and 4 lighting outlets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high and low voltage operation corridor is 1 meter wide, and there are doors that open outwards on all sides, which is very convenient for operation and maintenance;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZGS-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-American-style</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/zgs-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-american-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/zgs-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-american-style/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/20.png&#34; alt=&#34;ZGS-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-American-style&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
ZGS-12 intelligent integrated substation American box substation is also called prefabricated substation or prefabricated substation. It is a kind of high-voltage switchgear, distribution transformer and low-voltage power distribution device. It is a factory prefabricated indoor and outdoor compact power distribution equipment arranged according to a certain wiring scheme, which is to organically combine functions such as transformer step-down and low-voltage power distribution. Together, they are installed in a moisture-proof, rust-proof, dust-proof, rodent-proof, fire-proof, theft-proof, heat-insulating, fully enclosed, and movable steel structure box. It is suitable for urban network construction and transformation, and is a rising trend after civil substations. Brand new substation. The box-type substation is suitable for mines, factories, enterprises, oil and gas fields, and wind power stations. It replaces the original civil engineering power distribution room and power distribution station, and becomes a new type of complete power transformation and distribution device. The box-type substation is suitable for residential quarters, urban public substations, bustling downtown, construction power supply, etc. Users can choose box-type substations according to different conditions of use and load levels. Since the box type substation came out, it has developed extremely rapidly. In developed countries in Europe, it has accounted for 70% of distribution transformers, and in the United States it has accounted for 90%. With the rapid development of China&amp;rsquo;s urban modernization and the continuous renewal and transformation of urban distribution networks, it will be widely used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The product is small in size and beautiful in appearance. Easy installation, operation and maintenance, reliable operation. The transformer adopts a three-phase five-column structure, and the winding connection group adopts Dyn11 connection, which has the characteristics of low loss, low noise, zero-sequence voltage self-suppression, three-phase voltage mutual non-interference, good lightning protection performance, and strong unbalanced load capacity. . The high-voltage side uses plug-in dual-sensitive fuses and backup fuses to provide double protection for the transformer. The shell is made of high-quality steel plate, which has good corrosion resistance after special anti-corrosion process. Shell protection grade IP33.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
