<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control –  High Voltage Complete Set of Equipment</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-high-voltage-complete-set-of-equipment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  High Voltage Complete Set of Equipment on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-high-voltage-complete-set-of-equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HXGN15-12-box-type-fixed-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 17:18:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/hxgn15-12-box-type-fixed-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;HXGN15-12 (F), HXGN15-12 (F R) box-type fixed AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear), suitable for rated voltage of 12KV, rated frequency of 50HZ, rated current of 630A and above A three-phase AC system powered by network cabinets or radial terminals, used for segmenting and branching of cable lines. This product is equipped with FLN36-12D type sulfur hexafluoride load switch or FLRN36-12D type load switch-fuse combination electrical appliance with insulating shell, which has the advantages of small size, light weight, easy operation, light operation force, reliable interlocking and maintenance-free. It is a new generation of high-voltage switchgear required for the transformation and construction of urban power grids. The equipment is mainly used as distribution automation system for city power supply load center and cable power supply.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/25.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;HXGN15-12-box-type-fixed-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
The principle of ring network power supply: ring network power supply is generally composed of three basic units. The incoming and outgoing line cabinets are used as the ring network unit. When any line fails, it can be isolated in time, and the other unit maintains the continuous power supply of the certified user transformer branch. The user circuit ring network cabinet plays a role of protection and isolation for the transformer, which is convenient for maintenance and repair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet structure is assembled, stable and reliable, and easy to assemble. It can form a ring network power supply unit and various wiring methods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Small size, light weight, small footprint, easy to install.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet has three safe and independent compartments: the busbar room, the switch room and the instrument compartment. The cabinet body and each component have reliable safety grounding to ensure the personal safety of operators and maintenance workers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet can be equipped with FN12-12D, FN25-12D and other load switches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mechanical interlock is advanced and reliable, fully meeting the requirements of &amp;ldquo;five defenses&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ring network cabinet can be extended arbitrarily, and can be composed of basic units to form a variety of combination schemes according to user requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Five defenses&amp;rdquo; locking function&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power transmission operation: Only when the cabinet door is closed and locked, and the grounding switch is operated to the &amp;ldquo;open&amp;rdquo; position, can the load switch be operated to the closing position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power failure operation: When the load switch is in the isolation position, the grounding switch can be closed, and when the grounding switch is in the closing position, the cabinet door can only be opened after the insulating partition is inserted in place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a reliable interlock between the vacuum interrupter and the isolation knife, and the isolation knife and the grounding knife are interlocked with each other and interlocked with the cabinet door, and the insulating partition is also interlocked with the cabinet door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 16:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/kyn61-40.5-armored-mobile-ac-metal-enclosed-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/34.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KYN61-40.5(Z) armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear is suitable for power systems with a frequency of 50Hz, a rated voltage of 40.5kV and a rated current of up to 3150A. It has the functions of control, protection and monitoring of the circuit. Can be widely used in general power systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KYN61-40.5(Z) type armored removable AC metal-enclosed switchgear (hereinafter referred to as &amp;ldquo;switchgear&amp;rdquo;) is suitable for three-phase AC 5 0 Hz power systems, used in power plants, substations and industrial and mining enterprises The power distribution room is used to receive and distribute electric energy, and to control, protect and monitor the circuit.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/33.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KYN61-40.5-armored-mobile-AC-metal-enclosed-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product meets the standards: GB3906 &amp;ldquo;3~35kV AC metal-enclosed switchgear&amp;rdquo;, GB/T11022 &amp;ldquo;High-voltage switchgear and control equipment standard common technical requirements&amp;rdquo;, IEC60298 &amp;ldquo;rated voltage above 1kV and below 50kV AC metal-enclosed switchgear and control equipment &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integrated, miniaturized, and modularized product development with wide applicability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Five-defense&amp;rdquo; locking device design, safe and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet has strong anti-corrosion and anti-oxidation properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adopt balanced electric field measures, and the busbar is insulated with heat-shrinkable material, which has high insulation performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level can reach IP4X.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ambient air temperature: upper limit temperature +40°C. The lower limit temperature is -15°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Relative humidity: daily average relative humidity: ≤95%, daily average water vapor pressure not exceeding 2.2KPa; monthly average relative humidity: ≤90%, monthly average water vapor pressure not exceeding 1.8KPa;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Altitude: below 1000m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earthquake intensity: no more than 8°C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The surrounding air should not be significantly polluted by corrosive or combustible gases, water vapor, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No place with severe vibration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it is used under the normal conditions specified in GB3906, it shall be negotiated by the user and the manufacturer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
