<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – XJM Distribution Box</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/xjm-distribution-box/</link>
    <description>Recent content in XJM Distribution Box on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/xjm-distribution-box/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>XJM-metering-box-distribution-box</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xjm-metering-box-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 15:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/xjm-metering-box-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;XJM series metering boxes are suspended or embedded, suitable for the metering of one or more users in civil and commercial residences. The meter box has a multi-door structure, the main switch is installed in the left door, and the watt-hour meter is installed in the right door. , easy to operate.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/11.png&#34; alt=&#34;XJM-metering-box-distribution-box&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outdoor type is suitable for urban, rural, industrial and mining enterprises and other construction sites. It controls AC 50Hz, lighting lines below 500V, and functions as overload, short circuit protection and metering. The structure is completely bent and welded by stainless steel plates. The main structure is composed of box body, box top, box door and inner door. All parts are waterproof and anti-corrosion. There is a cable inlet and outlet hole at the bottom of the box, the size of the hole is standard, and the insulating rubber gasket is set inside, which is easy to knock off, and can also be specially opened according to the special requirements of the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The indoor type is suitable for general industrial and mining enterprises and production workshops, and is used for power lighting distribution of 500V and below, 50 Hz AC three-phase system. The structure is made of cold-rolled steel plate bent and welded. The structure of this product is mainly composed of box body, door panel, installation plate and other components. The box body can adopt single door or double door structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The main technical parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-main-technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-main-technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Main circuit rated voltage: 220V, 380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated insulation voltage: 400V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated frequency: 50/60Hz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rated current: 125A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protection class: IP30&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
