<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control –  High Voltage Switch Cabinet</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-high-voltage-switch-cabinet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  High Voltage Switch Cabinet on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:40:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-high-voltage-switch-cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LKGK-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 18:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/lkgk-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/3.png&#34; alt=&#34;LKGK-12-fully-enclosed-inflatable-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
LCGK-12 fully insulated and fully enclosed inflatable metal switchgear (referred to as inflatable cabinet) is also known as common box type inflatable cabinet, sf6 inflatable cabinet. All its live parts are completely sealed in a 3.0mm thick stainless steel SF6 gas box, multiple branch switches can be installed in one gas box, so that the switchgear is not affected by the environment. It truly realizes functions such as maintenance-free, reliable operation, and unattended operation. The inflatable cabinet unit adopts a modular design, which can be flexibly expanded and scientifically combined. It is a fully insulated and fully enclosed high-voltage switchgear. It is suitable for 50HZ, 12kv three-phase AC high-voltage power distribution system for receiving and distributing high-voltage electric energy. Because of its strong adaptability, it is widely used in mines, coastal areas, alpine plateau areas, airports, hotels, schools, subways, municipal construction and other industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fully insulated and fully enclosed, all live equipment in the inflatable cabinet is encapsulated in a stainless steel gas box, and the outgoing cables are connected by closed cable plugs, which can effectively isolate the environmental impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inflatable cabinet adopts a modular design, which can flexibly expand the unit, while occupying an area of more than 50% less than that of conventional high-voltage switch cabinets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level of the shell is high. The gas box of the inflatable cabinet is made of 3.0mm thick stainless steel plate welded by a welding robot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inflatable cabinet can choose electric operation or manual operation, and at the same time realize the remote monitoring function, with a high degree of intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The main technical parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;the-main-technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#the-main-technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflatable cabinet is a full name. It includes all unit cabinets. Commonly used are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unit C: load switch module. It is equivalent to the incoming line of the ring network cabinet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;F unit: load switch fuse combination module. Equivalent to the outgoing line of the ring network cabinet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;V unit: Vacuum switch module. Equivalent to a circuit breaker unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unit D: Cable connection module without grounding knife. Equivalent to a lift cabinet unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
