<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – European Style Substation</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/european-style-substation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in European Style Substation on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/european-style-substation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ZBW-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-European-style</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 19:40:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/zbw-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-european-style/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/21.png&#34; alt=&#34;ZBW-12-intelligent-integrated-substation-European-style&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
The box-type substation is a frame structure, which is welded with section steel; the shell is made of aluminum alloy plate, coated with special paint. There are four pull-out hanging bolts on both sides of the box-type substation base, and four lifting rope support cards on both sides of the top eaves of the box-type substation. This special design for hoisting greatly facilitates the safe hoisting of the substation and prevents the sling from scratching the casing, which is highly praised by users. The box substation is divided into relatively independent high and low voltage rooms and transformer rooms by steel plates. The low voltage room and transformer room can have corridors or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adopting three cooling measures: upper and lower natural wind convection, horizontal natural wind convection and bottom special fan forced air cooling, the temperature rise has a large margin;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Light weight, small size and high rigidity;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modularization: the high and low voltage electrical room, transformer room, metering box, and capacitor box are each formed into modules, which can be selected and combined according to user needs;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beautiful appearance, low noise, in harmony with the surrounding environment and increase the beauty;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Powerful functions, complete facilities, high voltage can meet the ring network power supply, low voltage room can have 8 power outlets and 4 lighting outlets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The high and low voltage operation corridor is 1 meter wide, and there are doors that open outwards on all sides, which is very convenient for operation and maintenance;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
