<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – GGD Switchgear</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/ggd-switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GGD Switchgear on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/ggd-switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/ggd-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinets can be widely used in power plants, substations, factories and mines and other power users. In the power distribution system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 380 V, and rated current up to 3150 A, it can be used as power, lighting and distribution systems. Electric energy conversion, distribution and control of electrical equipment.
&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/43.png&#34; alt=&#34;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt; &amp;ldquo;GGD-type-low-voltage-fixed-switch-cabinet&amp;rdquo;
GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet is a new type of low-voltage power distribution cabinet designed by our company based on the principles of safety, economy, rationality and reliability according to the requirements of the superiors in the Ministry of Energy, the majority of power users and the design department. The incoming lines include upper, lower, left, middle, right on the top of the cabinet and rear incoming lines to meet the actual needs of various projects for different incoming lines. At the same time, there is a fixed position in the cabinet for power plants and special users to install electromechanical protection and automatic devices. The product has the characteristics of high breaking capacity, good dynamic and thermal stability, flexible electrical scheme, convenient assembly, strong series and practicability, novel structure, high protection level, etc., and can be used as a replacement product for low-voltage complete switchgear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet body of the GGD AC low-voltage power distribution cabinet adopts the form of a general cabinet, and the frame is assembled by partial welding of 8MF cold-formed steel. quality. The components of the universal cabinet are designed according to the principle of modules, and there are 20 mold mounting holes, the universal coefficient is high, and the factory can realize pre-production. Not only shorten the production cycle, but also improve work efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The design of the GGD cabinet has fully considered the heat dissipation problem during the operation of the cabinet, so there are different numbers of heat dissipation slots at the upper and lower ends of the cabinet. When the electrical components in the cabinet heat up, the heat rises and can be discharged through the slots at the upper end. The cold air is continuously supplemented into the cabinet through the slots at the lower end, so that the sealed cabinet body forms a natural ventilation channel from bottom to top to achieve the purpose of heat dissipation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the requirements of modern industrial product modeling design, the GGD cabinet adopts the method of golden ratio to design the shape of the cabinet body and the division size of each part, so that the whole cabinet is beautiful and generous, and has a new look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet door is connected to the frame with a rotating shaft type living hinge, which is convenient for loading and unloading. There is a mountain-shaped rubber-plastic strip embedded in the hem of the door. When the door is closed, the strip between the door and the frame has a certain compression stroke, which can prevent the door from directly colliding with the cabinet body and improve the protection level of the door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The instrument door equipped with electrical components is connected to the frame with multi-strand annealed copper wires. The installation parts in the cabinet are connected with the frame by knurled screws, and the whole cabinet constitutes a complete grounding protection circuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The cabinet topcoat is made of polyester orange-shaped baking varnish, which has strong adhesion and good texture. The whole cabinet is in matt tone, which avoids the glare effect and creates a more comfortable visual environment for the staff on duty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top cover of the cabinet can be removed when necessary, which is convenient for the assembly and adjustment of the main busbar on site. The four corners of the cabinet top are equipped with lifting rings for lifting and shipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protection level of the cabinet is IP30, and the user can also choose between IP20~IP40 according to the requirements of the use environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
