<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control –  Low Voltage Switch Box</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-low-voltage-switch-box/</link>
    <description>Recent content in  Low Voltage Switch Box on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:36:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/-low-voltage-switch-box/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 10:36:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gck-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/42.png&#34; alt=&#34;GCK-type-low-voltage-withdrawable-complete-switchgear&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;
GCK low-voltage switchgear series is called combined low-voltage withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as switchgear). It is suitable for the power system of AC 50~60HZ, rated working voltage AC 380V, rated insulation voltage 660V, 1600KVA and below distribution transformer as power distribution, power, lighting, reactive power compensation, motor control center, and designed in the standard cabinet The mixed system of fixed scheme and withdrawal scheme can meet the different needs of users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This series of products has high breaking capacity, good dynamic and thermal stability, advanced and reasonable structure, practical electrical scheme, strong series and versatility;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Various program units can be combined arbitrarily, and one cabinet can accommodate more circuits, saving floor space, beautiful appearance, high protection level, safe and reliable, and convenient maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This product complies with the ICE439 standard and the national standard GB7251 &amp;ldquo;Low-voltage switchgear and control equipment&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The frame is made of special-shaped steel, and the three-dimensional plate is used for positioning, and the bolt is connected without welding structure, so as to avoid welding deformation and production stress, and improve the installation accuracy;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mounting holes of the frame and parts change according to the modulus E=25mm;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The internal structural parts are galvanized, and the exterior is sprayed with electrostatic epoxy powder after pickling and phosphating;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the power center (PC) incoming cabinet, the top is the horizontal busbar area, and the lower part of the horizontal busbar area is the circuit breaker room;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The inclination to the vertical plane shall not exceed 5°.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
