<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control – GZDW DC Control Panel</title>
    <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/gzdw-dc-control-panel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GZDW DC Control Panel on Global Expert in Mining Crushing and Electrical Control</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 14:26:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://www.senkuogroup.com/tags/gzdw-dc-control-panel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 14:26:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.senkuogroup.com/products/electrical-controls/gzdw-intelligent-high-frequency-dc-control-panel/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3&gt;Product Overview&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;product-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#product-overview&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/images/Complete-switch-cabinet/36.png&#34; alt=&#34;GZDW-Intelligent-High-Frequency-DC-Control-Panel&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GZDW series DC screen with cadmium nickel battery, floating charger, equipped with automatic detection and alarm device, has long service life, no pollution, convenient maintenance, stable voltage, ultra-low internal resistance output, withstand large current impact and strong adaptability, reliability Advanced features, it is an ideal DC operating power supply device, which can be widely used in substations of 500kV and below and power plants below, and can also be used in metallurgy, mining, petroleum, radio and television, computer rooms, underground railways, high-rise buildings In construction and other departments, it is used as DC control, signal power supply, power failure protection and circuit breaker operating mechanism opening and closing power supply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Performance characteristics：&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;performance-characteristics&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#performance-characteristics&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two-way AC input controlled by microcomputer can be switched automatically;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AC input overvoltage, undervoltage, overcurrent, phase loss and zero automatic detection, display and alarm protection;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The charging and floating charging device adopts intelligent high-frequency switching rectifier module, N+1 redundant combination, automatic current sharing, and can be plugged and unplugged;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The process of battery equalization charge and float charge is automatically switched, and it can operate normally according to the computer settings. Disconnection of the power grid, recovery of power transmission and other procedures realize the intelligent floating charge management of the battery;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the microcomputer control device fails or sends out wrong control commands, the charging module enters an autonomous working state, and the output voltage is the safe voltage set by the factory to ensure the reliability of the system operation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The intelligent four-remote system provides detailed communication protocols for AC input, DC output, battery circuit and expanded environmental monitoring, and has an intelligent interface for communication with the substation integrated automation system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Technical Parameters:&lt;span class=&#34;absolute -mt-20&#34; id=&#34;technical-parameters&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a href=&#34;#technical-parameters&#34; class=&#34;subheading-anchor&#34; aria-label=&#34;Permalink for this section&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Input voltage: AC380V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Output voltage: DC220, 110, 48, 24V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Battery capacity (larger): 3000AH&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maximum regular load current: 300A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Control bus accident load current: &amp;lt;300A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accident load time: 8b&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Number of feed-out channels: 4-6Track channels&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Closing bus, closing pulse current: 5000A&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Closing pulse time: 0.3h&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Number of feed-out channels: 4-6Track channels&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome global agents, distributors, retailers, and other partners to join us and work together to develop mutually beneficial business relationships. Our products have already been well received by customers in many countries and regions, and we look forward to expanding our reach even further.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.senkuogroup.com/contact/&#34; &gt;contact us&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sales@senkuogroup.com&#34; &gt;sales@senkuogroup.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
